{"data":[{"question":"The lion has long been a symbol of strength, power, and it is very cruel.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Until","b":"turns","c":"of","d":"on","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Turns-> turned","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"All the scouts got theirselves ready for the long camping trip by spending their weekends living in the open.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"last","b":"hurried","c":"the other","d":"did not have","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Hurried-> hurrying","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Nobody had known before the presentation that Sue and her sister will receive the awards for outstanding scholarship.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Before we returned","b":"had stole","c":"back","d":"around","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Had stole-> had stolen","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Alice Walker has written books of poetry and short stories, a biography and several novel.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"getting home","b":"for him","c":"dog","d":"up","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Dog barking-> barking dog","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Until his last class at the university in 1978, Bob always turns in all of his assignments on time.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has been hoped","b":"last","c":"to give","d":"one","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Had been hoped-> had hoped","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Before we returned from swimming in the river near the camp, someone had stole our clothes, and we had to walk back with our towels around us.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"After driving","b":"realized","c":"has been driving","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Has been driving-> had been driving","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Patrick was very late getting home last night, and unfortunately for him, the dog barking woke everyone up.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"are","c":"in","d":"opposite","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n\n- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"He has been hoped for a raise for the last four months, but his boss is reluctant to give him one.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"by","b":"are","c":"until","d":"after","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"After driving for twenty miles, he suddenly realized that he has been driving in the wrong direction.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of the","b":"know","c":"or","d":"for mounting","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Know-> knows","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The Department of Foreign Languages are not located in the new building opposite the old one.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Those of","b":"for","c":"their","d":"as possible","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Their-> his","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}